Looks like we ran into more
trouble than expected.
（誇山(こやま)）
思った以上に 手間取っちまったな
Claw
7th Division
You mean you did.
（桜威(さくらい)）
お前がな
You idiot! You only had
wimpy-looking ones to deal with.
（誇山）
バカ野郎！
お前のほうは 弱っちいのしか
いなかったんだろうが！
But I'm amazed you actually
managed to hurt Koyama.
（桜威）
しかし 誇山にケガを負わせるとは
お前 待遇いいかもしれんぞ？
You might get special treatment.
No, it wasn't him.
（誇山）
いや こいつじゃなくてさ
邪魔してきたヤツがスゲえ強くて
Another guy got in my way,
and he was really strong.
What? Another esper?
（桜威）
はあ？
ほかに超能力者がいたのか？
（誇山）
おう
Yeah. He was insanely strong for a kid.
ガキのくせに半端じゃねえ出力で
押し負けたから
お前のスプレー 使ったぜ
I couldn't match him in power,
so I used your spray on him.
And where is that kid?
（桜威）
そのガキは どうした？
I already had too much on
my plate, so I left him.
余裕ねえから置いてきたさ
This is exactly why I didn't
want to pair up with you.
（桜威）
だから お前と
組みたくなかったんだ
あ？ なんでだよ！
Huh? What do you mean?
何より強い能力を持つ子供を
さらうのが最優先だって
We had orders to make abducting kids
with the strongest psychic
powers our top priority!
さんざん指令が出てただろうが！
こんな大失態が
支部長に知られたら…
If the division leader found out
that you messed up like this...
面白そうな話をしてるな
This all sounds very interesting.
Let me in on it.
俺にも聞かせろよ 今の話
I'll make sure the division leader
doesn't find out.
（寺蛇(てらだ)）
支部長には
秘密にしといてやるからさ
"Claw" Upper Echelon:
Terada
And the worst possible person
just overheard us.
（桜威）
最悪のヤツに聞かれたな
～
Mob Psycho
"Claw"
~7th Division~
（運転手）
寺蛇さん
Terada-san, wouldn't it be better
to bring the other Scars here?
ほかの“傷”も連れてきたほうが
確実なのでは？
No, I'm all that's needed
from the upper echelon.
（寺蛇）
ううん 幹部は俺１人でいい
Koyama's an idiot,
but his abilities are the real deal.
誇山はバカだが 実力は確かだ
If that kid is an enemy,
he'll be a real handful,
そのガキは 敵ならやっかいだし
and if he joins us, he'll probably
surpass me, which also isn't good.
味方になれば
俺より出世しそうで困る
So this isn't a mission.
だから これは任務じゃねえ
We're just going to nip
some trouble in the bud.
出そうな芽をぶっ潰しに行くだけだ
Oh, by the way, this is a secret.
あっ これ 秘密な
Let's just say we're going
to capture him, kthx.
あくまでも 捕まえに行く体(てい)で
シクヨロ
Understood.
（運転手）
承知しました
What do you want to do, Kageyama-kun?
（テル）
どうする？ 影山(かげやま)君
We're dealing with a huge organization
with a lot of members.
向こうは大人数の組織だ
I think you're going to need
someone on your side.
（テル）
誰か 君の味方になる人間が
必要なんじゃないかな？
On my side?
（モブ）
味方？
Someone who's strong and extremely smart.
（テル）
強くて頭の切れる頼もしい仲間がさ
You know, like someone
right under your nose...
例えば ほら 目の前に…
The Body Improvement Club!
肉体改造部？
おい！
そこで別にボケなくていいから
Hey. You don't need to play the fool here.
僕しかいないだろ？
手伝ってあげるよ
Who else but me? I'll help you out.
えっ 花沢(はなざわ)君が？
Huh? You will, Hanazawa-kun?
（エクボ）
どういう風の吹き回しだ？
What brought this on?
I'm going to end up clashing
with Claw again someday.
（テル）
僕も いつかは
また“爪”とぶつかる日が来る
So I thought I might as well do it now
while I still have a fighting chance.
だったら 今 勝算のあるうちに
片づけてしまおうと思ってね
And by fighting chance, I mean you.
“勝算”ってのは君のことだよ
If you actually get serious about this,
there's no way we'd lose.
君が本気になれば
負けるはずがないんだ
（モブ）
あ…
And yet we have absolutely no clues.
（エクボ）
とはいえ 依然 手がかりは皆無
（密裏賢治(みつうらけんじ)）
私も手伝おう
必要な物があったら 言ってくれ
I'll help, too.
If there's anything you need, let me know!
No, that won't be necessary.
（テル）いや それは大丈夫
（密裏）えっ
どうせ すぐに来るはずだよ
次の刺客がね
Because the next attacker
should be showing up any second now.
マ… マズいじゃないか！
早く この場を！
That's not good!
You should hurry and—
（エクボと密裏）あっ！
思ったより早い
Well, that was quicker than I thought.
（寺蛇）
影山く～ん
Kageyama-kun...
Which one of you is the naughty little boy?
悪い子は ど～れだ
Why don't we ask him a few questions?
あの人にいろいろ聞こうか
（モブ）
うん
Okay.
（桜威）
寺蛇は例のガキに勝てると思うか？
Do you think Terada can
win against that kid?
寺蛇より俺のほうが強い
I'm stronger than Terada.
そんなことは聞いてない
勝てるかどうかの話だ
I don't care about that.
I'm asking you if he can win.
あいつは用心深いヤツだ
He's a really cautious guy.
As strong as that kid was,
he was still only a kid.
例のガキは強いといっても
子供だった
If I hadn't let my guard down, I could've
easily squashed him right at the get-go.
油断しなきゃ
立ち上がりの段階で簡単に潰せた
Terada will probably be fully prepared.
寺蛇は盤石の構えで いくだろう
So that kid's probably going to
go through some harsh torture.
あのガキは 恐らく その場で
きつい拷問にかけられるだろうな
ばあ～ ああ～ うう～！
Hurry up and spit it out.
さっさと吐け
I let my guard down!
（寺蛇）
油断した～！
He seems out of breath.
苦しそう
一旦 休ませて
水でも飲ませたほうがいいんじゃ？
Why don't you take a break and
let him have a sip of water?
You don't realize how cruel
that suggestion is, do you?
君も なかなか天然な鬼畜だな
You don't have to be nice
to scum like these.
いいんだよ
外道には優しくしなくても
Still, he really won't talk...
それにしても
なかなか口を割らないなあ
I guess the Scars, Claw's upper echelon,
live up to their name.
さすが“傷”と呼ばれる
幹部なだけはある
Despite going up against the boss
and ending up with a scar,
ボスに逆らって傷を負いつつも
their abilities were acknowledged,
and they became part of the upper echelon.
その実力を認められ
幹部の位を得た者たち
And then you, Terada,
heard about the kid who gave Koyama,
その“傷”の１人である誇山を
退けた子供の情報を
いち早く聞きつけてやって来た
お前 寺蛇が
another Scar, some trouble and showed up.
Yet you yourself ended up
being captured and tortured.
逆に捕まって
拷問を受けているというこの事態に
If you feel you're in trouble, you should
tell us everything you know, quickly.
危機感を感じているなら
早めに 持っている情報を
全部 出したほうがいいぞ
I did! I did!
吐いてる 吐いてる！
Everything you just said is
information that I gave you!
今 言ったセリフ
全部 俺が吐いた情報でしょうが！
Secret Hideout Location
Names of Members
Abilities
Etc.
うん アジトの位置も
Yeah.
We found out where their hideout is,
この人が知ってるかぎりの
構成員の名前と能力も
the names and abilities of the members,
ほかにも いろいろと
引き出せたよ
and various other things.
いいや こんな簡単に
秘密を吐くなんて信じられない
Nah... I can't believe he'd
tell us everything so easily.
What am I supposed to do?
（寺蛇）
俺 どうしたらいいの？
We're not starting yet?
（誇山）
まだかよ！
It's past the time for our regular
upper echelon meeting,
定例幹部会議の時間 過ぎてんのに
11人中７人しか集まってないって
おいおい
and yet only seven out of
the eleven are even here.
I've got to wonder about
Claw's management system.
“爪”の管理体制を疑うねえ
Terada went off somewhere,
so he should be fired.
寺蛇なんて 出かけちまったしよ
クビにしちまえ～！
"Claw" Upper Echelon:
Muraki
（邑機(むらき)）
お前らも
今 来たところだろうが
You two also just showed up.
Yeah, and you were thirty minutes late.
（無飼(むかい)）
そうそう
30分も遅れてね
"Claw" Upper Echelon:
Mukai
We're a gathering of people who
never worked well with others.
（嶽内(たけうち)）
もともと歯車になど
なりえん連中が
集まったんだ
"Claw" Upper Echelon:
Takeuchi
やるべきときに
やるべきことをなせば
As long as we do what we need to do
when we need to do it, it's fine.
一向に かまわん
（宮蛾輪(みやがわ)）
ケッケッケ～
"Claw" Upper Echelon:
Miyagawa
Then I guess you're out, Koyama.
じゃ 誇山 アウトだな～
中学生に負けたんだってな？
I heard you lost to a middle schooler.
I didn't lose, and I did my job.
負けてねえし 自分の仕事はした
You really are a simpleton.
"Claw" Upper Echelon:
Tsuchiya
（槌屋(つちや)）
相変わらず 単細胞だね
You really need to stop playing around—
あんた 本当に
遊びは ほどほどにしないと…
うるせ～ ブス！
Shut it, fugly!
Huh? I'll kill you, you pierced chicken.
（槌屋）
あ？ 殺すぞ チキンピアス
You what?
Sit down, Koyama.
誇山 席に着け　支部長が来た
The division leader is here.
Did you wait long?
I just got a message from the boss.
（遺志黒(いしぐろ)）
待った？
"Claw" 7th Division Leader:
Ishiguro
さて ボスから連絡があったよ
Said he's coming back to Japan next month.
来月 日本に帰ってくるって
Seems he's going to pick a couple of you
to be the upper echelon back at HQ.
この第７支部からも１～２名
本部の幹部に抜擢(ばってき)する予定だってさ
なに？ そりゃ ホントか？
What? Are you serious?
Yes, but it looks rather doubtful
that he'd pick you,
（遺志黒）
そうだけど 君は望み薄かもね
今日の失敗を考えると
considering how badly you messed up today.
（誇山）
うっ…
That's right!
（教育係１）
そう！ つまり 目的は世界征服！
Basically, our goal is world domination.
（教育係１）
“能あるタカは爪を隠す”というが
我々は そうではない
They say a skilled hawk hides its claws,
but we're not like that.
We'll be hawks who don't hide our claws.
爪を隠さないタカとして
奪う物は全て奪い
We'll steal everything we can,
stand at the top of the world,
この世界のトップに立ち
人類を正しい未来へと
導いていくのだ！
and lead humanity into its rightful future!
Are any of you going to join us?
（教育係２）
我々に同調する者は？
いないんだな？
（影山 律(りつ)）
バカバカしい
How stupid.
はあ～！
おいおい ナチュラルのガキども
Hey, you Natural brats...
（教育係３）
あまり私たち教育係をナメるなよ
Don't underestimate your trainers.
You noobs haven't even been
acknowledged as members yet.
（教育係１）
お前ら新入りは
まだ構成員と認められてもねえんだ
あっ
Are you in charge here?
We don't have psychic powers.
あなた 上司の人ですか？
僕たち 超能力なんてありません
何かの間違いだから
家に帰してください
This is some kind of misunderstanding,
so please let us go home.
Did you all secretly agree to act
like you don't have psychic powers
（霧藤(むとう)）
超能力を
持ってないことにしようと
"Claw" Upper Echelon:
Muto
口裏を合わせたのか？
so you'd be freed?
解放されるために
（律）
うっ…
（霧藤）
いいだろう
Very well. You, come out here.
お前 出てこい
（白鳥海斗(しらとりかいと)）
えっ？
（朝日(あさひ) 豪(ごう)）
白鳥 弟
The younger Shiratori brother.
You have ten seconds.
（霧藤）
10秒以内だ
能力を見せろ 早く
Show me your powers. Be quick.
（白鳥大地(だいち)）
うう…
Don't do it.
（律）
見せちゃダメだ
All right, I understand.
（霧藤）
お前らの態度は よく分かった
I'll show you just what you get
if you look down on me.
来い
ナメたらどうなるか 見せてやる
K-Kaito!
（大地）
か… 海斗！
ああ…
They're going to try to
brainwash us one by one.
（律）
１人ずつ 洗脳教育する気だ
Why is this happening?
（黒崎(くろさき) 麗(れい)）
なんで こんなことに？
I'm done with this...
もう嫌だ
（海斗）
うわああああ！
Daichi-oniichan!
大地お兄ちゃ～ん！
Help me!
助けて～！
ぐぎゃっ！
Huh? What was that?
（麗）
えっ 何？ 今の
Th-That was Kaito...
か… 海斗の 弟の声だ
My younger brother's voice...
あっ
（一同）
あっ！
H-He's dead...
（律）
し… 死んでる
This is going to happen to you, too.
（霧藤）
お前らも すぐこうなる
Take the night to reconsider
your attitudes...
ひと晩よく考えて 態度を改めろ
まだ死にたくなければな
If you don't want to die, that is.
（一同）
あああ…
I see it. It's that building, right?
（テル）
見えた　あの建物だな？
Y-Yeah...
そ… そうだ
These powers can't be coming from a child...
（寺蛇）
子供とは思えんパワーだ
うひっ！
オーケー ここからは徒歩で行こう
Okay. Let's walk from here.
（寺蛇）ううっ…
Ah. Terada ran away.
あっ 寺蛇が逃げた
Should we go after him?
（エクボ）
追うか？
（テル）
う～ん
Considering how badly we beat him,
I'm sure he won't try to defy us again.
あれだけ こてんぱんにされたら
もう刃向かってこないだろう
It'd just be a waste of time,
so let's just save your little brother.
時間のムダだし
僕らは さっさと弟君を救出しよう
You stupid brats...
ガキども
俺のプライドを踏みにじった罪
You'll pay with your lives
for trampling all over my pride!
死をもって償え！
Telekinetic control.
（寺蛇）
念力操作
Air Whips.
空鞭(からぶち)！
Air Whips
With a maximum range of sixty meters,
最大射程 60メートル！
my powers will display their
true potential in this environment!
この環境下で
俺の力は真価を発揮する！
（エクボ）
ん？
おりゃ～！
（テル）
うっ… うう…
影山君 生きてるかい？
Kageyama-kun, you alive?
Yeah, but that startled me.
（モブ）
うん ビックリした
なんで空から木が？
Why did trees fall from the sky?
It's that guy.
（テル）
あいつだ
He said he used telekinetic powers
in the shape of whips.
鞭(むち)のような念動力を使うって
言ってた
Say your prayers, brats.
（寺蛇）
覚悟しろ ガキども！
Terada!
（テル）
寺蛇！
If I let you infiltrate
the facility like this,
（寺蛇）
このまま 施設に侵入されたら
メンツが丸潰れなんだよ！
my reputation will be ruined!
（テル）
くっ うっ ふっ…
うおっ！
Got you!
（寺蛇）
つ～かまえた～
（テル）
うっ
フッフフフ～
くっ！ 何だ 結構 使うじゃ…
Well, I guess you aren't so lame after—
あっ
マズい！
Crap!
うっ ううっ…
Not bad, huh? Think you can hold up?
なかなかのパワーだろう？
君に さばけるかな？
K-Kageyama-kun,
（テル）
か… 影山君
僕が鞭に集中している間に
while I'm concentrating on
the whip, do something!
何とかしてくれ！
I guess there are a lot of ways
to use powers.
（モブ）
いろんな力の使い方があるんだね
（寺蛇）うわっ！ ぐわあ～！
ハア…
Apparently technique means nothing
before absolute power.
（テル）
圧倒的な力の前には
小手先の技術は通用しない
You were finished as soon as
Kageyama-kun considered you an enemy.
影山君の敵意に触れたのが
運の尽きだな
This battle will only last a night.
戦いは ひと晩で終わる
Mob Psycho
Let's escape.
（律）
脱出しよう
（星野(ほしの)武史(たけし)）
影山
Kageyama!
You saw what happened!
If we defy them, we die!
お前も見ただろう？
逆らったら 殺されちゃうんだよ
捕まってでもみろ　そしたら…
Think about it. If they catch us...
No! Don't say any more!
いや！ 言わないで！
If I'm going to be shackled by fear
and brainwashed,
恐怖で縛られ
洗脳されるくらいなら
I'd rather try to escape,
even if it means I could die.
僕は今 死ぬ気で
逃げ出したいよ
But Shiratori's still grieving.
でもな まだ白鳥だって傷心してる
立ち直るのにも時間が…
It'll take him a while to get over this.
Shiratori-kun, help us escape.
白鳥君 脱出に協力してくれ
Hey, Kageyama!
おい 影山！
Yeah, I want to escape, too.
うん 僕も脱出に賛成
（武史）
えっ？
Huh?
Apparently, my younger brother is fine.
（大地）
どうやら 弟は無事だよ
We brothers are telepaths.
僕ら兄弟はテレパシスト
離れてても 意思疎通できる
We can communicate
even if the other is far away.
I was just talking to him now.
今も弟と交信してた
Apparently he was shown our corpses.
弟のほうは
僕ら５人の遺体を見せられたらしい
多分だけど あの男の力は
幻覚を植え付ける催眠能力
I'm not completely sure,
but I think that guy has hypnotic powers
that show us illusions.
He's probably the key to this organization's
ability to brainwash people through fear.
この組織の
恐怖洗脳の要になってるんだと思う
分断されたのが
テレパシーの通じる弟でよかった
It's a good thing he took my brother,
who I can talk to telepathically.
生きてるのか！
So he's alive...
でも ヤバい組織だっつう事実は
変わらないだろ？
But that doesn't change the fact that
this is a dangerous organization.
And that's exactly why
we can't stay here long.
（律）
だからこそ
ここに長くいちゃいけないのさ
We'll strike tonight,
脱出するなら今夜
while the trainers are
still underestimating us.
教育係が
まだ僕らを甘く見てるうちにだ
H-Hey, those guys are discussing something.
あっ おい あいつら
何か話し合ってるぞ
Are they plotting to escape?
まさか 脱出の算段か？
Let them. It's no use anyway.
させておけ
どうせムダなあがきだ
I know it's a terrible time
to bring this up...
今更 悪いんだけどさ
What's wrong?
（武史）
どうした？
Before I tell you all my plan,
what were your,
僕の考えを説明する前に
君たちの…
um...
えっと…
names again?
名前 何だっけ？
S-Seriously?! You didn't even
remember our names?!
お前… ウッソ？
俺らの名前すら
覚えてなかったのか？
君 何 考えてるか
分からなかったからな～
You always were hard to read
with that gloomy face of yours...
暗い顔して
（麗）
まあ まあ
Now, now...
I guess we'll just have to
introduce ourselves again.
じゃあ 改めて
自己紹介していきましょ
私は黒崎 麗よ
特技は超直感力
I'm Kurosaki Rei.
My specialty is clairvoyance.
Pleasure to work with you, Kageyama-kun.
よろしく 影山君
Likewise.
（律）
よろしく
I'm Hoshino Takeshi.
星野武史だ
超強力な念動力を使える
I have super strong telekinetic powers.
朝日 豪
I'm Asahi Go.
全てを焼き尽くす
“火炎の申し子”と呼ばれている
I'm called the godsend who can
burn everything in his path.
By whom, exactly?
（律）
誰にだろう？
２人とも よろしく
Pleasure to work with you both.
白鳥大地っていいます
I'm Shiratori Daichi.
連れていかれたのが弟の海斗です
The guy who got taken away
is my little brother Kaito.
Let's hurry up and rescue Kaito-kun
and get the heck out of here.
早く 海斗君を救出して
ここから脱出しよう
But do you have a plan?
（武史）
何か策はあるのか？
Also, the trainers are right there.
（豪）
それに目の前で
教育係が見張ってるじゃないか
I think they already know that
we're trying to escape.
（律）
脱出の意思があるってことは
既にバレてると思う
I'm sure there were other kids
who tried to do the same thing.
今までだって
逃げようとした子は いただろうし
じゃあ
対応に慣れてるってことじゃない？
That would mean they're used to
dealing with escape attempts.
余計 望みが薄くなってきたわ
There goes any chance we had.
That's not entirely true.
それは違う
僕らの力を甘く見てれば
きっと脱出できる
If they're underestimating our powers,
we'll be able to escape.
How?
どうやって？
They probably let their guard down
because we're kids.
子供だと思って油断したんだろう
They didn't check our belongings.
手荷物検査は されなかった
Do you really carry that around everywhere?
お前 いつも持ち歩いてるのか？
Ignite!
着火！
うう… うわあ！
今だ 星野！
Now, Hoshino!
よし きた！
All right!
There!
ほい！ ふんぎゅぎゅぎゅ…
うおおおおお！
Oh, it opened.
あっ 開いた
やってみるもんだな
I guess everything's worth a shot.
（拍手）
Well done, brats.
（教育係１）
お見事だな ガキども
で？
What now?
What's your next move?
そこから どうするんだ？
ど… どうするんだ？ 影山
Wh-What's our next move, Kageyama?
Let me just warn you that
it's safer in that cell.
牢屋(ろうや)の中にいるほうが安全だぞ
If you step even one foot out of there,
we're going to have to discipline you.
（教育係２）
一歩でも出たら 我々が教育する
影山？
Kageyama?
Are you telling me you didn't
plan this far ahead?
もしかして この先 ノープラン？
Let's use Hoshino-kun's
super strong telekinesis
星野君の超強力な念動力と
朝日君のファイヤーで突破しよう！
and Asahi-kun's fire to get out of here.
（教育係たち）
ナッハハハハハ！
Well, isn't that adorable?
（教育係１）
かわいいこと言ってるぞ ウヒ～！
Listen...
あのな…
念動力で人間大の重さのものを
you can't move something as heavy
as a person with telekinesis.
動かせるわけねえだろ
Even though I'm a pyrokinetic genius,
（豪）
パイロキネシスの天才の俺でも
I don't think I can set fire
to something that's moving.
動いてるものを発火させるのは
ちょっと無理かも
I'll take care of it, then.
じゃあ 僕がやるよ
Huh?
（一同）
え？
Though I'm nowhere near as good as you guys.
（律）
２人には とても及ばないけどね
Come on. Get out, everyone.
ほら みんなも出なよ
（教育係１）
ハハ どうせ連帯責任だ
You'll all be held responsible either way.
Do you think we'd hold back
on you because you're kids?
子供だと思って
俺たちが手加減するとでも？
思ってないよ
No.
Why would I ever expect incompetent,
disposable lackeys like you
あなたたちのような
無能な消耗人材が
to have that kind of common sense?
そんな良識
持ち合わせてるわけないじゃないか
Y-You're going to be killed, Kageyama.
（武史）
こ… 殺されるぞ 影山！
I see.
（教育係１）
そうかい
じゃあ お得意のスプーン曲げで
自分を守ってみろや
Well, try protecting yourself with the
spoon-bending that you're so good at,
Mr. Natural!
ナチュラルさんよお！
Please, powers...
（律）
頼む 僕の“力”
言うことを聞いてくれ！
Do as I say.
たあ！
うわっ
（教育係たち）
ぐわっ！
うげっ！
ハア…
Wh-Whoa...
（武史）
ス… スゲえ
You probably didn't need us
to open the lock...
俺たちに鍵を開けさせるまでも
なかったんじゃ…
No, we needed to show them
that we were powerless.
（律）
いや 僕らが非力であることを
見せる必要があった
（武史）
ええ？
This is a blind spot for
that security camera.
（律）
あの監視カメラから ここは死角
Let's have them think
we're being disciplined for a while
長めの教育をされていることにして
早く海斗君を救い出そう
and quickly go rescue Kaito-kun.
But I don't know where Kaito is.
でも 海斗が
どこにいるか分からない
黒崎さん ここからは
君の直感力だけが頼りだ
Kurosaki-san, now we're going to
have to rely on your clairvoyance.
Huh? Me?
えっ 私？
頼めるかな？
Can we count on you?
や… やってみます
I-I'll try...
Th-This is lame...
（朝日と星野）
お… 面白くねえ！
There're some tough-looking guys
standing by the entrance.
（エクボ）
入り口にゴツいのが立ってるな
What do you wanna do?
どうしようか？
Shigeo, you need to think, too.
茂夫(しげお) お前も考えるんだぞ！
Want to blow them away?
（テル）
ぶっ飛ばすかい？
Those strangers.
（エクボ）
あそこの他人をよ
（モブ）
あ… あああ…
り… 律を助ける方向で
L-Let's concentrate on rescuing Ritsu.
I knew it.
（エクボ）
やっぱりな
Okay.
オーケー
おっ その技は
That technique...
It's the Air Whips I just learned earlier.
さっき覚えた
空鞭！
（守衛係たち）
うわっ！
ああ～！
うわっ うわあああ！
ぐっ…
Sorry.
悪いね
It's easier to possess someone
when they're in shock.
（エクボ）
気が動転してる瞬間は
精神を乗っ取りやすい
You seem used to this, Dimple-kun.
（テル）
手慣れてるな エクボ君
Are you a pretty dangerous evil spirit?
結構 危険な悪霊なのか？
Of course not. Right, Shigeo?
めっそうもない
なあ？ 茂夫
Dimple's dangerous.
エクボは危ないよ
We might've been better off
if you'd possessed Terada.
どうせなら 寺蛇の体を乗っ取れば
有利に事が運びそうなのに
Espers all have mental protection on them,
（エクボ）
超能力者は みんな
精神プロテクトが かかっててな
so they're hard for evil spirits to possess.
悪霊に乗っ取られにくくなってる
That goes for you guys, too.
それは お前らも同じだ
Not to mention, I'm a lot weaker right now.
だが 俺様が かつてないほど
弱っているせいでもある
Usually, I'd be able to
destroy people's minds.
ふだんだったら
軽く精神破壊できるぜ
You weren't a big deal before, either.
以前も
全然 大したことなかったけど？
I was weakened then, too!
あん時も
弱ってたんだっつうの！
Why are you weakened?
（モブ）
なんで 弱ってるの？
Because you almost exorcised—
（エクボ）
お前に除霊されかけたときに…
Never mind.
もういいよ
All right! Let's go!
（テル）
よし 突入だ！
All right, we're good.
We're counting on you, Kurosaki-san.
（律）
よし 大丈夫だ
黒崎さん 頼む
うん
Okay.
This way next.
次は こっちよ
Let's go.
（律）
行こう
All right, let's keep going.
よし 進もう
（モブ）
うん
Okay.
（構成員）
ん？ 何者だ？
Who're you?
Huh?
あっ ああ… うわっ
Hey, are you trying to kill him?
おいおい 殺す気か？
It's because we both hit him at once.
２人同時に当てたせいだ
Listen up, Kageyama-kun.
いいかい？ 影山君
雑魚の制圧は僕に任せて
Leave all the grunts to me.
まずは
弟君の幽閉場所を聞き出さないと
First, we have to find out where
they're holding your brother first.
Oh, right. Sorry...
あっ そっか　ごめん
His casual attitude is throwing me off.
This is supposed to be a tense situation.
（テル）
緊迫する状況なのに 調子 狂うな
（構成員）
何だ？ お前ら
Who are you?!
うおっ
You abducted some kids, didn't you?
子供たちを さらってきただろ？
彼らの居場所を教えろ
Tell us where they are.
うっ うう… 子供は 地下…
The children are in the basement...
He said the basement.
地下だってさ
茂夫！ 律は ここにいるってよ
Shigeo, apparently Ritsu's here.
（構成員）
うわあ～！
Thank goodness.
よかった
You fools. We can hear you over the radio.
（構成員）
バカめ 無線で筒抜けだ
We've got intruders. After them.
侵入者だ　向かい撃て
Wait. Contact the Scars, too.
（構成員）
待て！ “傷”にも連絡しておけ
They might be espers.
超能力者かもしれない
An emergency, huh?
（桜威）
緊急事態か
It's gotta be him.
（誇山）
あいつしか いない
That means Terada got his ass kicked.
寺蛇は
まんまとやられたってわけだ
First Koyama, and now Terada...
誇山に続いて 寺蛇までもが？
What's going on?
どうなってんだ？
おい 俺は
負けたわけじゃねえって！
Hey! I didn't lose!
Terada just rushed into things!
寺蛇が勝手に先走ったんだろうが！
あいつは俺がやる！
I'll take care of him.
こんなに早く
再会できるなんて
I'm delighted beyond words that
I get to see him again so soon.
うれしくて
たまらねえぜ
Are you saying we should
leave him to just you?
お前１人に任せろというのか？
Of course! Stay outta my way, you bastards!
（誇山）
当然だ！ 邪魔すんなよ てめえら
Don't rush into things.
There's more than one intruder.
（桜威）
先走るな　侵入者は１人じゃない
So what?
（誇山）
だから 何だ？
You're going to lose again.
また負けるぞ
Sakurai... You wanna die first?
桜威 先に殺されてえのか？
Stop it. You're both Scars.
やめなよ “傷”同士で
That's fine, Koyama-kun.
（遺志黒）
いいよ 誇山君
Go ahead.
行っておいでよ
But you won't get away with losing
to the same person twice.
でも 同じ相手に
二度も負けるなんて 許されないよ
分かってるよ
I know that.
Now we're up against the clock.
（テル）
ここからは時間との勝負になる
Let's split up and find your brother.
別々に弟君を捜そう
僕は右を行く
影山君は真ん中…
I'll go right.
Kageyama-kun, go down the middle.
ん？
（エクボ）げっ！
（モブ）あ…
Gah.
Ah.
Crap, the mini boss just appeared.
ヤベえぞ
いきなり 中ボス登場かよ
I see...
なるほど 確かに
（誇山）
また会ったな
We meet again.
I beat the crap outta you,
and you can already move?
あんなにボコったのに
もう動けるのか？
Well, I'm glad you're doing well.
まあ 元気そうで何よりだ
I'll kill you this time...
今度は ちゃんと殺してやるよ
For real.
本気でな
２人で一気に
フルパワーでぶつけよう！
Let's both hit him with our
full powers at the same time.
We don't have time right now.
今は余裕がないんだ
You don't have time? What?
（誇山）
余裕がない？
You're trying to reserve your stamina?
おいおい スタミナを
温存しておきたいっつう話か？
この俺を前にして？
When you're facing me?
ヘッ… ハハハハハ
ア～ハッハハハ！
You stupid brats!
クソガキが～！
来た！
He's coming!
あっ
Huh?
うわっ
（誇山）
うっ… 何だ？
指１本 動か… ない
What? I can't move a finger...
ああ…
うわっ！
Sorry for being so noisy.
（モブ）
ごめん 大きな音 立てて
I see...
そうか 相手に気を遣う余裕が
ないってことか
You meant that you didn't have time
to try to hold back on him...
Didn't expect that from Kageyama-kun.
（テル）
あの影山君が…
Koyama's not responding.
（桜威）
誇山から応答がない
We're definitely dealing with
someone powerful.
相手は間違いなく強い
ケッ 哀れなヤツ
How pathetic.
Let's go...
行くぞ
Show the intruders the true terror of Claw.
侵入者に“爪”の恐怖を刻んでやれ
～
Mob infiltrates Claw's hideout
along with Teru,
（霊幻新隆(れいげんあらたか)）
頭頂部150パーセントのテル
不気味な風船エクボと共に
who has 150% on top of his head,
and the creepy-looking balloon, Dimple.
“爪”の支部に乗り込んだモブ
They end up facing the Scars,
who childishly refuse to hold back.
そんな３人に幹部の“傷”たちが
大人気もなく襲いかかる
Are you going to be able to win this, Mob?!
勝算あるのか？ モブ
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 Episode 10:
次回「モブサイコ100」
第10話
“巨悪のオーラ　黒幕”
"The Heinous Aura ~Mastermind~"
The serious option C involves
Blu-rays, manga volumes, and events!
本気のＣコースだと
ブルーレイ 単行本 イベント！
The Heinous Aura
~Mastermind~